Triple Frontier is a action, thriller, crime film directed by J.C. Chandor.
Struggling to make ends meet, former special ops soldiers reunite for a
high-stakes heist: stealing $75 million from a South American drug lord.
Tom 'Redfly' Davis, played by Ben Affleck.
Santiago 'Pope' Garcia, played by Oscar Isaac.
William 'Ironhead' Miller, played by Charlie Hunnam.
Ben Miller, played by Garrett Hedlund.
Francisco 'Catfish' Morales, played by Pedro Pascal.
Yovanna, played by Adria Arjona.
Triple Frontier is a 2019 American action-adventure film directed by J.
Chandor, who co-wrote the screenplay with Mark Boal.
The film stars Ben Affleck, Oscar Isaac, Charlie Hunnam, Garrett
Hedlund and Pedro Pascal as a group of former U.S.
Army Delta Force operators who reunite to plan a
heist of a South American crime lord.
The film was released by Netflix in theaters on March 6, 2019,
before a worldwide streaming release on March 13, 2019.
It received generally favorable reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of peru, cocaine, amazon
rainforest, survival, drug cartel.
The tone is intense.